gamesahara.com 2016-04-02

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**For gamemeteor.com**

-

Effective Date: April 23, 2013

Last Modified: March 24, 2015

**1\. General**

**1.1.** The website gamemeteor.com ('Site') is brought to you by Flora ICT B.V. ('We', 'Us', 'Our'). We receive personal information about Our Site's visitors ('You', 'Your'). This Privacy Policy is intended to explain to You what personal information We collect and what We do with that information. This does not include information that did not reach Us through Your use of the Site. We care much about Your privacy, therefore We do Our best to comply with relevant laws and regulations regarding the processing of personal data, such as the Dutch Data Protection Act (Wet Bescherming Persoonsgegevens). By visiting Our Site, You automatically agree to the terms stated in this Privacy Policy.

**2.** **What (personal) information do We collect?**

 **2.1. Active collection**

The Site does not provide memberships, subscriptions or any other means that lead to an agreement between You and Us. Therefore We do not actively collect Your personal data. In the event that You come across a feature of this Site that requests Your personal information (for example a registration request, membership form or discussion board), You should be aware that this is a request originating from a third party, not from Us, and We can not be held responsible for any use of Your personal data by a third party. With that said, We may temporarily collect Your personal data when You decide to provide this to Us when using one of Our report features. For example, You may voluntarily provide Us with Your emailaddress when reporting malware.

**2.2. Passive collection**

The Site passively collects personal data through cookies. A cookie is a small file that is being delivered to You through the pages of this Site and that is being stored on Your computer. The information stored on this cookie is being sent back to Us each time You visit Our Site. Cookies help Us to deliver Our visitors a better, _personalized_ experience on Our Site. The information We collect through Our cookies includes Your IP Address, browser user agent details, geographical locations and any other data that is related to Your visit of Our Site. We do Our best to anonymize this personal data as much as possible and We store this information only for as long as necessary regarding the purpose for which these cookies are being placed. Your browser settings allow You to block and/or delete certain cookies. If You do not agree to the use of cookies, We recommend that You change Your preferences and use the right browser settings. Changing these settings and preferences may limit Your ability to take full advantage of Our Site.

For more information about how to adjust Your cookies in Your browser settings:

  * Internet Explorer (<http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11>)
  * Google Chrome (<https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>)
  * Mozilla Firefox (<https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer#w_cookie-settings>)
  * Safari (<https://support.apple.com/kb/ph17191>)

**3\. Which cookies do We use?**

 **3.1.** **Persistent cookies**

By using a persistent cookie We can recognize You when You visit Our Site. The Site can therefore be tailored to Your preferences. Also, when You have given consent for the placing of cookies, We can remember this by means of a cookie. This way You do not have to repeat Your preferences every time You visit Our Site, thus saving time and making Your use of Our Site more pleasant. Persistent cookies can be removed through the settings of Your browser.

**3.2. Session cookies**

By using a session cookie, We can see which parts of the Site You have viewed during Your visit. With that information, We can optimize and adapt the Site as much as possible to the surfing behavior of Our visitors. These cookies are automatically deleted when You close Your web browser.

**3.3. Analytical cookies**

This websites uses analytical cookies to track and get information about Your visit to this Site. First, we place Our own analytical cookie. The information in this cookie has a short retention period and any information, such as IP-address, is anonymized as much as possible. We do not share this information with third parties, unless we are required to do so to satisfy any laws, regulations or other legal purposes. We may disclose aggregated and non-personal information to third parties to operate Our services properly.

Second, an analytical cookie is placed as part of Our Use of the service Google Analytics. Google may transfer this information to third parties only when required by law or in cases where third parties process the information on Google's behalf. We have no influence on this. We have not allowed Google to use the information acquired through the analytical cookies for other Google services. The information Google collects, such as Your IP-address, is anonymized as much as possible. The information is transmitted to Google and stored on its servers in the United States. Google states that it complies to the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the Safe Harbor principles, regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. This means that there is an adequate level of protection for the processing of any personal data. We have concluded a Data Processing Agreement with Google for their Google Analytics service.

**3.4.** **Tracking cookies**

**3.4.1.** **Advertising cookies**

Third parties may place an advertising cookie to offer You interest based advertisements. These cookies may collect information about Your browsing activity across multiple online services and websites, to offer You advertisements based on Your interests. These cookies do not include Your name, address, email etc., but solely the information needed to build a profile about Your online surfing behaviour to make sure You receive relevant advertisements. We have no control over these cookies and what information they collect.

For example: Google Adsense, an advertising service provided by Google, delivers a"DoubleClick"-cookie to You, which tracks Your use of this Site and Your behavior concerning advertisements, products and the services We offer. This results in the offering of advertising to You based on Your prior website visits and interests. You can manage Your "DoubleClick"-cookie settings here:<http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en>

For more information on interest based advertising, cookies and opting-out:

  * <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/>
  * <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

Please note: opting-out for interest based advertisements may still result in the appearance of standard, non-interest based advertisements on the Site.

**3.4.2.** **Social media cookies**

Third parties, such as Facebook and Twitter, may place social media tracking cookies. These cookies may collect information about Your browsing activity across multiple online services and websites and offer You social media sharing options. We have no control over these cookies and what information they collect. For more information on social media cookies, how third parties use them and which (personal) data they collect, please check the (privacy) policies of the respective social networks regularly:

  * <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>
  * <https://twitter.com/privacy/>
  * <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy>

**4.** **Our use of Your personal information**

 **4.1.** The passively collected, aggregated and non-personal information collected through cookies is being used for market research, marketing purposes, to optimize Our Services and to optimize Your experience on Our Site.

**4.2.** We do not provide third parties with Your personal information, or information regarding Your use of the Services or Site(s) accesible through Our services, unless this is strictly necessary in Our sole discretion, and We believe that it is reasonable to do so, including:

i) To satisfy any laws, regulations or legal requests for such information;

ii) To disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Our Terms of Use or other policies;

iii) To operate Our services properly;

iv) To protect Ourselves, Our Site's visitors, and the general public. We specifically reserve the right to disclose any and all information to law enforcement in the event that a crime is committed, is suspected, or if We are compelled to do so by lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, writs, or reasonable request of authorities or persons with the reasonable power to obtain such process;

v) To cooperate with law enforcement authorities, government agencies and/or private-party litigants seeking information about Our users, to the extent required by applicable law and/or if We are legally advised to do so. Examples of such cooperation include but are not limited to, lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, writs, or reasonable request of authorities or persons with the reasonable power to obtain such process.

**5\. Security**

 **5.1.** We take Your privacy serious and therefore We have taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to prevent and minimize the risk of unauthorized access, inappropriate use and inaccuracy of (personal) data stored on Our network and systems, insofar as this is reasonably possible and expected of Us. However, given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals, We are unable to guarantee that Our security is one hundred percent (100%) breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite Our reasonable security measures.

**6\. Third party websites**

 **6.1.** This Privacy Policy does not cover any processing of personal data from websites that are linked to or from this Site. We cannot guarantee that those third parties have the same level of caution and trustworthy in handling personal data. We recommend that You read the privacy policies of those websites before You enter, or when You leave, Our Site.

**7\. Public Forums & interactive communication**

 **7.1.** If at any time during Your visit to the Site, You enter into a public forum or interactive communication feature such as, registration requests, chat sessions, or discussion boards, You have exited Our Site. We do not provide such features on Our Site, therefore, You understand and agree that the Site is not responsible for any content shared or distributed via such interactive features.

**8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

 **8.1.** We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that You regularly visit this page and check if You have read the latest version of the Privacy Policy, which is indicated by the 'Last Modified' date stated above. Please refresh Your browser when You re-visit this page to make sure that Your browser shows You the latest version of this Privacy Policy.

**9\. Who are We?**

 **9.1.** Flora ICT B.V. Is a Dutch company, based in Haarlem. Our services mainly consist of providing webtraffic to Our clients. Our contact information: Flora ICT B.V.

Wagenweg 40

2012 NE, Haarlem

The Netherlands

+31 (0)23 5298683

Company Registration#: 57378320

VAT# : NL852554564B01

**10\. Any Questions?**

 **10.1.** If You have any questions about Our Privacy Policy or about the inspection, modification and/or removal of Your personal information, please contact Us on: [support@floraict.com](mailto:support@floraict.com)

\- End -

Â© Flora ICT B.V.
